{
    "subject": "resource/Rustichelli_&_Bordini",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Italy",
    "human_readable": "Rustichelli & Bordini are from Italy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9851037859916687,
            "question": "Are Rustichelli & Bordini Italian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9840654730796814,
            "question": "Is Italy the origin of Rustichelli & Bordini?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9288271069526672,
            "question": "Where are Rustichelli & Bordini from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9151340126991272,
            "question": "From which nation are Rustichelli & Bordini?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8135674595832825,
            "question": "What country do Rustichelli & Bordini hail from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7974355220794678,
            "question": "Where were Rustichelli & Bordini born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7853018045425415,
            "question": "Rustichelli & Bordini's origins are in what location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7484422326087952,
            "question": "To which nationality do Rustichelli & Bordini belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.736045777797699,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Rustichelli & Bordini?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7127940654754639,
            "question": "Can you identify the home country of Rustichelli & Bordini?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rustichelli & Bordini are from Italy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7818_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Rustichelli & Bordini?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7818_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which nationality do Rustichelli & Bordini belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7818_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rustichelli & Bordini's origins are in what location?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7818_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7818_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention several Italian bands and musicians, including references to Rustichelli & Bordini. Given that the context is about Italian progressive rock groups and their activities in Italy during the 1970s, it supports the statement that Rustichelli & Bordini are from Italy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}